Guide to the Peter McCandless papers, 1978-1992
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 6: News Releases, 1980-1990; (3 boxes)
  - Reston Land Corporation Press Releases, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Construction Starts on Reston Parkway Improvements", December 13, 1989; 4.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "GRACE Receives $2,500 from Mobil Foundation", July 28, 1989; 5.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Guilfole and Schultz Promoted", September 1, 1989; 6.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Mobil Foundation Contribution Helps Reston Community Players, Inc.", August 9, 1989; 7.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Mobil Foundation Gift Supports Student Homebuilders", June 9, 1989; 8.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Mobil Foundation's Fifth Year Gift Enables YMCA to Expand Valuable Teenage Programs", May 26, 1989; 9.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Mobil Land Development (Virginia) Corporation Takes Title to 1219 Loudoun County Acres", February 3, 1989; 10.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Mobil's Twentieth Birthday Gift To Reston Interfaith", September 8, 1989; 11.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Net New Leasing Activity Tops Half Million Square Feet", July 21, 1989; 12.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Reston Fellowship Foundation Receives Mobil Foundation Gift", November 30, 1989; 13.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Reston First Quarter Office Leasing Action Tops Last Six Months of 1988", May 5, 1989; 14.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Reston Land Corporation Selects the Martin Organization", July 7, 1989; 15.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Reston Marketing Brochure Wins Finalist Award in New York", June 16, 1989; 16.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "Schmergel Joins Reston Land Corporation Marketing", November 17, 1989; 17.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "The Urban Land Institute Recognizes Reston, Virginia With Distinguished Award for Excellence", October 27, 1989; 18.
    - Press Release: Reston Land Corporation, "The Urban Land Institute Recognizes Reston, Virginia With Distinguished Award for Excellence", October 27, 1989; 19.
    - Press Release: Tetra Partnerships, "First Ownership Opportunity Ever Opens on Reston Pond", February 27, 1989; 20.
    - Tetra Partnerships, "Tetra Hires Coho to Market Pond", February 3, 1989; 21.
    - Press Release: The McCandless Company, "Ethics, Leadership and the Bottom Line Featured at May 25 GMU Executive Forum", May 3, 1989; 22.
  - Reston Parkway Improvements, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    298.4
  - Robinson Wins Virginia Lions 41st Blaud Music Competition, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    297.2
  - Cheek Appointed to Northern Virginia (NOVA)/National Association of Industrial and Office Parks (NAIOP) Board, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    297.1
  - Reston Marketing Brochure Wins Finalist Award in New York, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    297.3
    - Reston Marketing Brochure Wins Finalist Award in New York (News Release), 16 June 1989; 1.
  - Hall Year Leasing, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    297.4
  - Mobil Foundation Fax, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    296.12
  - John Wolf, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    297.6
  - Keu Orski, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    297.7
  - Reston Board of Commerce (RBC) Netherton History, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    297.17
  - Reston Land Corporation Selects The martin Organization, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    297.11
  - First Quarter Leasing Activity, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    296.8
  - Frutchey and Miller, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    296.6
  - Mobil Land Development (MLD) of Virginia Moves Into Loundoun County, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    296.4
  - Connell Appointed Executive Director, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    297.14
  - Reston Board of Commerce (RBC) Media Releases, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    297.15
  - Mobil Gift to Reston, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    299.13
  - Third Quarter Net Absorption, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    299.14
  - Mobil Grant to Reston Association/Environment, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    299.7
    - $500 Grant Letter from Mobil Foundation to Reston Environmental Education Foundation, Inc., August 2, 1990; 1.
    - Photograph: Vernon J. Walker Nature Center Expansion Ceremony, September 15, 1990; 3.
    - Vernon J. Walker Nature Center, ca. 1990; 9.
  - Milligau Appointed Mobil Land Development Corporation (MLDC) Virginia Business Planner, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    299.6
  - Reston Lands Awards From New York City, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    299.5
  - Mobil's Gift $3000 to Grace Art Gallery, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    295.4
  - Town Center New HOme for Reston Developer, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    299.3
    - Reston News Release: Reston Town Center New Home for Reston Developer, June 18, 1990; 1.
  - Autumwood Park Pool Inaugural, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    299.2
  - Community Appearance Alliance Awards Reston Land Corporation, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Chili's Comes to Reston Cinema, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    299.9
  - Bill Ewing and Steven Hines, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Reston Land Corporation gives Nine Acres in Reston Town Center (RTC) to Park Authority, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Mobil Gives Nine Acre Deed as Gift to Reston Town Center Park, October 19, 1990; 1.
    - Reston Land Presents Gift of Nine Acres to Park Authority to Provide Recreation Facility in Town Center, October 19, 1990; 3.
  - Weekend Debut of Halstead Glenn II, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    299.12
  - New Reston pathway Link Opens, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    299.8
    - New Pathway Link Opens, Closing the Last Gap Between Reston Town Center and Lake Anne, September 28, 1990; 1.
  - Mobil Christmas to Salvation Army, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Steiner Judges Fame in Florida, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    298.6
  - Mobil Land Development Corporation (MLDC) Virginia Hires Larry Phelps, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    298.7
  - Reston Aims Member of the Institute of Residential Marketing (MIRM) in Atlanta, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    298.8
  - Davison Moves to Reston Land Corporation, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Mac Benton Appointed Mobil Land Development Corporation (MLDC) Virginia, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    298.10
  - Reston Roadways Beautification, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    298.5
  - Reston Land Corporation Press Releases, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    456.2
  - Reston Reports Net Absorption at 401, 208 Square Feet Represents 10% of Northern Virginia, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    299.18
- Series 7: Reston Land Corporation Newsclippings, 1986-1992; (16.5 boxes)
  This is the largest series in the collection. Included in the collection are newsclippings to the Reston Land Corporation from different newspapers.
  - Final Week December, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    300.1
  - Second Half January, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    300.2
  - January First Two Weeks, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    300.3
  - Last Two Weeks February, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    300.4
  - First Half February, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    300.5
  - March, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    300.6
  - First Half March, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    300.7
  - Last Week of March and First Week of April, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    301.1
  - Last Week of April and First Week of May, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    301.2
  - Last Week of April and First Week of may, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    301.3
  - Last Two Weeks of April, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    301.4
  - First Two Weeks of April, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    301.5
  - First Two Weeks of May, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    301.6
  - First of June, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    302.7
  - Mid-June, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    302.1
  - End of June and First Week of July (Masters), 1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    302.2
  - Last Weeks of July and First Week of August, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    302.3
  - Last Two Weeks of August, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    302.4
  - First Two Weeks of August, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    302.5
  - Last TWo Weeks of September, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    302.6
  - First Two Weeks of September, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - First Two Weeks of October, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    302.8
  - November, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    302.9
  - November, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    303.1
  - The Connection-The Newspaper of Reston, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    303.2
  - Reston Growth Report, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    303.3
  - Final Two Weeks, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    303.4
  - First Two Weeks of December, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    303.5
  - Last Week of January and First Week of February, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    303.6
  - National Association of Industrial and Office Parks (NAIOP) January, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    303.7
  - Last Two Weeks of February, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    303.8
  - Last Two Weeks of March, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    303.9
  - First Two Weeks of March, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    303.10
  - Last Two Weeks of April, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    304.1
  - First Two Weeks of April, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    304.2
  - End of May and First Two Weeks of June, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    304.3
  - May, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    304.4
  - End of June and First Week of July, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    304.5
  - July 20 to August 31, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    304.6
  - First Two Weeks of August, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    304.7
  - Mid-August, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    304.8
  - August 18 to September 5, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    304.9
  - September 7-21, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    304.10
  - September 15-17, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    305.1
  - September 28 to October 5, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    305.2
  - October 7 to 23, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    305.3
  - October 13 to 28, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    305.4
  - October 31 to November 10, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    305.5
  - Three Weeks of November and First Week of December, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    305.6
  - November 12 and 23, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    305.7
  - November 30 to December 7, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    305.8
  - Last Two Weeks of December, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    306.1
  - January, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    306.2
  - January 16 to 30, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    306.4
  - End of February to First Week of March, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    306.5
  - February 2 to 15, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    306.6
  - February 13 to 23, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    306.7
  - Week of March 20, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    306.8
  - Late March and Early April, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    306.9
  - March 3 to 15, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    306.10
  - April 3 to 17, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    306.11
  - April 18 to May 9, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    306.12
  - May 10 to 22, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    306.13
  - May 24 to June 14, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    307.1
  - June 18 to 24, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    307.2
  - June 25 to 30, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    307.3
  - July 3 to 10, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    307.4
  - July 10 to 29, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    307.5
  - July 12 to 22, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    307.6
  - July 27 to August 5, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    307.7
  - August, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    307.8
  - August 4 to 13, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    307.9
  - August 11 to 23, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    307.10
  - September 1 to 6, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    307.11
  - September 11 to 18, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    308.1
  - September 18 to October 9, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    308.2
  - October 23 to November 6, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    308.3
  - November 13 to 24, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    308.4
  - November 26 to December 6, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    308.5
  - December 4 to 18, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    308.6
  - December 13 to 20, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    308.7
  - December 21 to January 4, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    308.8
  - January 1 to 15, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    306.3
  - January 17 to 24, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    308.9
  - January 24 to February 1, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    309.1
  - January 25 to 29, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    309.2
  - February 1 to 8, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    309.3
  - February 2 to 21, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    309.4
  - February 5 to 15, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    309.5
  - February 23 to March 1, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    309.6
  - March 3 to 8, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    309.7
  - March 5 to 18, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    309.8
  - March 21 to 27, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    309.9
  - March 28 to April 20, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    309.10
  - March 29 to April, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    310.1
  - April 21 to May 4, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    310.2
  - April 23 to May 9, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    310.3
  - May 3 to 18, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    310.4
  - May 17 to 24, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    310.5
  - May 25 to 30, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    310.6
  - June 4 to 6, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    310.7
  - June 11 to 22, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    310.8
  - June 20 to July 9, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    310.9
  - July 10 to 19, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    311.1
  - July 18 to 23, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    311.2
  - July 22 to 26, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    311.3
  - July 27 to August 3, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    311.4
  - August 3 to 8, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    311.5
  - August 15 to 18, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    311.6
  - August 22 to 27, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    311.7
  - August 27 to September 5, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    311.8
  - September 5 to 15, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    311.9
  - September 13 to 26, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    311.10
  - September 13 to 21, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    311.11
  - September 26 to October 6, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    311.12
  - October 5 to 11, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    312.1
  - October 11 to 24, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    312.2
  - October 12 to 22, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    312.3
  - October 25 to November 2, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    312.4
  - October 25 to November 9, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    312.5
  - November 8 to 16, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    312.6
  - November 17 to 30, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    312.7
  - November 30 to December 7, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    312.8
  - December 10 to 14, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    313.1
  - December 17 to 21, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    313.2
  - December 20 to January 3, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    313.3
  - January 7 to 18, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    313.4
  - January 17 to 35, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    313.5
  - January 24 to February 1, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    313.6
  - February 3 to 8, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    313.7
  - February 7 to 15, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    313.8
  - February 17 to 21, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    313.9
  - February 26 to March 5, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    313.10
  - March 8 to 15, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    313.11
  - March 18 to 22, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    314.1
  - March 21 to 29, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    314.2
  - April 1 to 5, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    314.3
  - April 8 to 12, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    314.4
  - April 15 to 21, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    314.5
  - April 23 to 26, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    314.6
  - April 26 to May 6, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    314.7
  - May 3 to 17, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    314.8
  - May 7 to 12, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    314.9
  - May 16 to 31, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    310.10
  - May 20 to 24, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    314.11
  - May 27 to June 7, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    315.1
  - June 10 to 14, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    315.2
  - June 13 to 27, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    315.3
  - June 17 to 21, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    315.4
  - July 1 to 7, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    315.5
  - July 8 to 12, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    315.6
  - July 12 to 19, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    315.7
  - July 19 to 24, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    315.8
  - July 31 to August 14, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    316.1
  - August 5 to 20, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    316.2
  - August 23 to 30, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    316.3
  - September 2 to 7, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    316.4
  - September 9 to 14, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    316.5
  - September 12 to 19, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    316.6
  - September 20 to 28, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    316.7
  - September 27 to October 4, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    316.8
  - October 7 to 11, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    316.9
  - October 12 to 25, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    317.1
  - October 28 to November 1, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    317.2
  - November 2 to 15, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    317.3a
  - November 2 to 15, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    317.3b
  - November 2 to 15, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    317.4a
  - November 2 to 15, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    317.4b
  - November 18 to 22, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    317.5
  - November 25 to 29, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    318.1
  - November 28 to December 6, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    318.2
  - December 11 to 14, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    318.3
  - December 18 to 27, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    318.4
  - December 19 to January 2, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    318.5
  - January 6 to 18, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    318.6
  - January 10 to 31, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    318.7
  - February 1 to 17, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    318.8
  - February 14 to March 2, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    318.9
- Series 8:General Information, 1979-1990; (5.5 boxes)
  This series contains a variety of topics including current media lists, House Beautiful Reston Land Corporation 20th Anniversary and others.
  - Real Estate Literature, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    456.6
  - Current Media Lists, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    277.8
  - Reston Town Center File, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    292.4a
  - Reston Town Center File (Including Architectural Competition), 1982 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    292.4b
  - Reston Land Corporation Information, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    279.3
  - Reston Land Corporation Current Work In Progress, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    279.4
  - October Billing, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    279.2
  - Maryland Life Magazine Article (July-August Issue), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    280.5
  - November Billing, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    279.1
  - Northern Virginia Builders' Association (NVBA) Action (Cover Story Photos), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    279.8
  - House Beautiful Reston Land Corporation 20th Anniversary, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    278.3a
  - House Beautiful Reston Land Corporation 20th Anniversary, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    278.3b
  - House Beautiful/Seminar Series, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    278.4
  - Peter L. McCandless/Public Relations, December Billing, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    278.6
  - Media Contacts, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    277.9
  - Tetra/Consearch/Vista/La Salade, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    287.6
    - Comsearch For Excellence - A Headquarters Unlike All The Rest, June 5, 1985; 1.
    - "'Hometown' Reston Savings Bank Opens, Bucking Industry Trends", November 11, 1985; 10.
    - Photograph: Comsearch Headquarters, no date (1985?); 6.
  - Action File: Deliver to Reston Land Corporation May Events, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    286.2
  - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    280.2
  - Norther Virginia Builders Association Raffle House File, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    282.9a
  - Northern Virginia Builders' Association Raffle House File, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    282.9b
  - Audio Tape-Interview with Robert E. Simon, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    456.3
  - NASA Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    294.14
  - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    292.7
  - First Quarter Homes Sales Best In Reston Land Corporation History/Ryland, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    284.5
  - Reston Child Care, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    280.4
    - Child Care in Reston: Present Status and Future Needs 1986 to the Year 2000, December 2, 1986; 1.
  - Reston Town Center-Grand Opening, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    283.5a
  - Reston Town Center-Grand Opening, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    283.5b
  - Miscellaneous NASA Pictures, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    295.3
  - NASA in Reston/Walker Company, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    295.4a
  - NASA in Reston/Walker Company, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    295.4b
  - Reston Land Corporation Schools and Community Profiles, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Realtor Alert Notes, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    292.2
  - 50,000 Resident Event, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    291.2
    - 50,000 Resident Event Invitation, November 14, 1987; 1.
  - Dulles/Reston at 25:Space Station New Dominion Magazine, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    289.3
  - Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    283.2
  - Masters, Reston Lake Newport Pool-Grant Opening, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    283.3
  - Lake Newport Pool-Grant Opening, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    283.4a
  - Lake Newport Pool-Grant Opening, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    283.4b
  - Reston Land Corporation Starts Reston Parkway, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    294.1
  - Reston History, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    293.5
  - Fellowship Foundation, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    293.8
  - Central Park, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    297.12
  - Realtor Alert Files, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    296.1
  - Judy Maun, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    297.16
  - Wedgewood Grand Opening with 20% Sold, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    299.21
  - Friday Home Report-Opens Four New Community, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    299.23
  - Half Year Projections Met/3 Months, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    299.22
  - Reston History, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    457.4
    - Memo: Peter McCandless to Fran Steinbauer, Dan Watt, Mike Was, Tom Grubisch, and Bill Steiner, "Reston at Twenty Frontispiece", January 14-26, 1985; 1.
    - Paper: Michael Leyzorek, "Robert E. Simon, Jr.: Conservator of Carnegie Hall, Creator of Reston", June 8, 1990; 2.
  - Reston History, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    457.5
  - Reston Town Center, 1990s (Box 34, Folder 3)
    456.4
    - Reston Town Center, February 1985; 1.
    - Illustration: Reston Land Corporation, "Reston Town Center Streetscape" (b and w), no date; 2.
    - Illustration: Reston Land Corporation, "Reston Town Center Streetscape" (color), no date; 3.
    - Photograph: Reston Land Corporation, "Reston Town Center Model", no date; 4.
    - Photograph: Reston Land Corporation, "Reston Town Center Model", no date; 5.
    - Plan: Reston Land Corporation, "General Plan Town Center Study Area Reston, Virginia", February 1985; 6.
  - Lake Newport Pool (Contact Sheets), 1990s (Box 34, Folder 4)
    455.1